>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 你一定是在问自己，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: You certainly must
be asking yourself at this point,
但那箭的功能呢
but, what about arrow functions?
我们的好友是箭的作用
Our good friend the arrow function.
让我们返回箭头函数并在以下内容的上下文中对其进行检查
Let's come back to arrow functions and
examine them within the context of what
我们刚刚讨论过这个关键词
we've just discussed,
which is the this keyword.
在这里，您会注意到我在工作坊对象上有一个提问方法。
Here you'll notice that I have
an ask method on my workshop object.
在它里面，我正在将回调传递到 setTimeout 和
And inside of it, I'm making
a callback pass to setTimeout and
它是一个箭头函数
it's an arrow function.
当调用箭头函数时，此关键字
And that this keyword,
when the arrow function is invoked,
正在正确地指向研讨会对象。
is correctly is pointing
at the workshop object.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这就是我们所说的词法。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: This is what we
refer to as lexical this behavior.
让我明确地为你解释一下这意味着什么
So let me clearly state for
you what lexical this means,
这个话题有很多困惑。
there's a lot of confusion
around this topic.
很多人心里都有一个心理模型，
Many people have in their
minds a mental model that
箭头函数本质上是硬约束函数
a arrow function is essentially
a hardbound function
给家长的这个不准确的。
to the parents this, that is not accurate.
思考一个箭头函数的正确方法
The proper way to think about
what an arrow function is,
箭头函数根本不定义此关键字。
an arrow function does not
define a this keyword at all.
在箭头函数中不存在此关键字之类的内容。
There is no such thing as a this
keyword in an arrow function.
这意味着如果你把这个关键词放进一个箭头函数中
Which means if you put a this
keyword inside of an arrow function,
就会像其他变量一样
it's gonna behave exactly
like any other variable.
这意味着它将在词法上解析为外层
Which means it's going to lexically
resolve to some enclosing
定义此关键字的作用域。
scope that does define of this key word.
那么当这个特殊情况，箭头函数线 5 ，当我们说
So when this particular case,
the arrow function line 5, when we say
这个点没有这个箭头的函数，不管它是怎么调用的，所以
this dot there is no this in that arrow
function no matter how it gets invoked, so
我们在词法上建立一个作用域，它是一个函数吗 ?
we lexically go up one level of
scope which is, which function?
>> 扬声器 2: [INAUDIBLE]。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [INAUDIBLE].
>> Kyle Simpson: 请求函数。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The ask function.
讲习班不是一项职能，讲习班是一个对象。
Workshop is not a function,
workshop is an object.
它从回回函数，箭头函数，
It goes out from the call back function,
the arrow function,
覆盖范围的范围，是吗 ?
that scope to the enclosing scope,
which is?
问，这个关键词的定义是什么 ?
Ask, and what is asks definition
of the this key word?
什么代码行控制此关键字在询问中指出的内容。
What line of code controls what the this
keyword will point out inside of ask.
第 10 行，因为此关键字的请求函数由调用站点设置。
Line 10, because the ask functions this
keyword gets set by the call site.
然后当那个回叫被重新调用时，它基本上就被关闭了。
And then when that call back gets later
invoked, it’s essentially closed over.
具有指向研讨会对象的此关键字的父作用域。
That parent scope that had a this
keyword pointing at the workshop object.
这就是我们的词法。
That's what we mean by lexical this.
这不是难以约束的功能。
It's not a hard bound function.
它是一个完全没有这个功能的功能。
It's a function that
doesn't have a this at all.
它是在词法上旋转的，这意味着如果它必须上五个级别，
And so it revolves lexically, that means
if it had to go up, five levels because
你有五个嵌套的箭头功能，就是不停地去
you had five nested arrow functions,
it just keeps going and going and going up
建筑物升降机，直至找到定义该关键字的函数。
the building elevator until it finds
a function that defines a this keyword.
无论这个关键的关键点是什么，都是它所使用的。
And whatever the this keyword points at
for that function, that's what it uses.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这不是一个正确的解释
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That is just not
the correct explanation to describe it and
最近有很多人在推特上跟我争论说，
many people have been arguing with
me recently on Twitter saying,
但这不重要
,but it doesn't matter.
是这样而且这里是规范的规范
Yes it does and
here is the spec, the spec says,
箭头函数未定义本地绑定
an arrow function does not
define local bindings for
参数 super 此值或 new.target。
arguments super this or new.target.
有时人们喜欢拍摄信使
People sometimes like
to shoot the messenger.
我没写规格
I didn't write the spec.
我只是在告诉你这个规范是什么好吗
I'm just telling you what the spec says,
okay?
该规范表示没有此关键字。
The spec says there is no this keyword.
所以我觉得你最好的结果就是你觉得像电脑
So I think the best outcome for you is
when you think like the computer instead
试图发明你自己的解释那也许会有偏差
of trying to invent your own explanations,
that may or may not deviate and
创造，让错误的思考和错误永久化。
create, and
perpetuate wrong thinking and bugs.
我之前在课程里说过
I've said this earlier in the course.
当你不正确地思考一个密码是如何工作的时候
When you think incorrectly about
how a piece of code works,
即使是在那一刻意外地工作你也不正确
even if it accidentally works
at that moment, you're incorrect
思维会导致更多虫子被感染
thinking will systemically lead
to more bugs down the line.
只有一个人能解决这个问题
And there's only one fix for that.
就像 JavaScript 认为的那样
It's to think, like JavaScript thinks.
这就是为什么我不断地在这个过程中反复引用。
That's why I keep referencing in this
course over and over and over again.
那个规范说什么
What does the spec say?
而且这也很重要
And it matters what the spec says so
我们不能把我们的大脑从错误的轨道上思考，思考一些事情。
that we don't get our brains off on
the wrong track and think about something.
你可能不认为一个箭的功能没有硬的界限
You might not think it would ever matter
that an arrow function's not hard bound.
这里有个非常疯狂的角落
Well here's a really crazy corner
case where it could matter.
记住这个关键词的行为
Remember how that this keyword behavior,
新关键字比硬绑定函数更有先例。
the new keyword is more precedent
than a hardbound function.
因为某种疯狂的原因，如果你在一个硬的函数上调用新的
That somehow for some crazy reason,
if you call new on a hardbound function it
将覆盖硬绑定并使其成为新对象。
overrides the hardbound and
it makes it the new object.
猜猜当你对一个箭头函数进行新的调用时发生了什么。
Guess what happens when you
call new on an arrow function.
如果一个箭头的功能很硬你应该能在一个箭头上
If an arrow function's hard bound, you
ought to be able to call new on an arrow
函数并覆盖它的这个关键字。
function and override its this key word.
当你调用一个箭功能的时候会发生什么呢，任何人之前都试过吗 ?
What happens when you call new on an arrow
function, anybody ever try that before?
你其实是有例外的
You actually get an exception.
不允许在箭头功能上调用新项。
You're not allowed to call
new on an arrow function.
所以这不是一个硬性的功能。
So it's not a hard bound function.
>> Kyle Simpson: 它是在此关键字上未定义的函数。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It is a function
that doesn't define on this keyword.